http://www.nativeaccess.com/privacy

Welcome to Aboriginal Access to Engineering, Queen's University
EducationAcademic Requirements
Academic & Social Support for Indigenous Students in Engineering
EducationAcademic Requirements
Academic & Social Support for Indigenous Students in Engineering
EducationAcademic Requirements
Academic & Social Support for Indigenous Students in Engineering
Privacy
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you subscribe to our email updates or fill out a form. When subscribing to our email updates or filling out a form on our site, as appropriate, you will be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To improve our website (We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)To improve customer service (Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)To send periodic emails (The email address you provide for email updates will be used to send you emails when news and events are posted to the website. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.)Do we use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.aboriginalaccess.caYour ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:Aboriginal Access to EngineeringFaculty of Engineering and Applied Science Queen's University Room 200, Beamish-Munro Hall 45 Union Street, Kingston Ontario K7L 3N6Tel: (613)-533-6000 ext.78563
Contact Details
Aboriginal Access to EngineeringFaculty of Engineering and Applied Science Queen's University Room 200, Beamish-Munro Hall 45 Union Street Kingston, Ontario K7L 3N6Tel: (613)-533-6000 ext. 78563
Aboriginal Access to Engineering at Queen’s University
We are committed to increasing the number of Indigenous engineers in Canada. Learn More
Sign up for our mailing list
Email Address *
Have Questions?
Call us at 613-533-6000 ext. 78563 or email us.
© 2020 Queen's University Aboriginal Access to Engineering. All Rights Reserved.
